<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<shows>
    <show>
        <name>Tabatha Takes Over</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Bravo</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>100 Questions</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>100 Questions (originally known as 100 Questions for Charlotte Payne) is an American situation comedy series which premiered on NBC on May 27, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>10 Things I Hate About You</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>18 to Life</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>18 to Life is a Canadian television sitcom that debuted on January 4, 2010 on CBC Television.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>2 Broke Girls</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>24</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>24 is an American television series produced for the Fox Network and syndicated worldwide, starring Kiefer Sutherland as Counter Terrorist Unit (CTU) agent Jack Bauer. Each 24-episode season covers 24 hours in the life of Bauer, using the real time method of narration. Premiering on November 6, 2001, the show spanned 192 episodes over eight seasons, with the series finale broadcast on May 24, 2010. In addition, the television movie 24: Redemption was broadcast between seasons six and seven, while a feature film of the same name is also planned.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>30 Rock</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>30 Rock is an American television comedy series created by Tina Fey that airs on NBC. The series is loosely based on Fey's experiences as head writer for Saturday Night Live. 30 Rock takes place behind the scenes of a fictional live sketch comedy series depicted as airing on NBC; the name "30 Rock" refers to the address of the building where NBC Studios is located, 30 Rockefeller Plaza.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>666 Park Avenue</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>90210</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>90210 is an American teen drama television series developed by Rob Thomas, Jeff Judah and Gabe Sachs, and the fourth series in the Beverly Hills, 90210 franchise created by Darren Star. 90210 is the first series produced by CBS Productions under the company's re-launch, but is now produced by CBS Television Studios. The series premiered on The CW on September 2, 2008 with a two episodes </description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>According to Jim</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>According to Jim is an American sitcom television series starring Jim Belushi in the title role as a suburban father of three children. It originally ran on ABC from October 3, 2001 to June 2, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ace of Cakes</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on food network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Ace of Cakes is an American reality television show which airs on the Food Network. The show focuses on the daily operations of Duff Goldman's custom cake shop, Charm City Cakes, in Baltimore, Maryland; including small-business ownership, working with various vendors, tasting with customers, constructing cakes, and delivering his products.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Adventure Time</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:00:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Alcatraz</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Alcatraz is an upcoming American television series starring Sarah Jones and Jorge Garcia. Bad Robot Productions produced the pilot episode, which is based on a screenplay by Elizabeth Sarnoff, Steven Lilien and Bryan Wynbrandt.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>All My Children</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 13:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>All My Children (abbreviated as AMC) is an American television soap opera that aired on ABC from January 5, 1970 to September 23, 2011. The show has been picked up by a third-party production company with plans to relaunch the program in the future as a web series.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Alphablocks</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 09:15:00(GMT+0 +DST) on CBeebies</airtime>
        <status> Status: TBD/On The Bubble</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 5 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Alphas</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Alphas is an American science fiction dramatic television series created by Zak Penn and Michael Karnow. The series follows a group of people with superhuman abilities, known as "Alphas", as they work to prevent crimes committed by other Alphas.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Amazing Race</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Amazing Race is a reality television game show in which teams of two people, who have some form of a preexisting personal relationship, race around the world in competition with other teams. Contestants strive to arrive first at "pit stops" at the end of each leg of the race to win prizes and to avoid coming in last, which carries the possibility of elimination or a significant disadvantage in the following leg. Contestants travel to and within multiple countries in a variety of transportation modes, including planes, balloons, helicopters, trucks, bicycles, taxicabs, rental cars, Jeepneys, trains, buses, boats, and by foot. The clues (cryptic hints) provided in each leg lead the teams to the next destination or direct them to perform a task, either together or by a single member. These challenges are related in some manner to the country wherein they are located or its culture. Teams are progressively eliminated until three are left; at that point, the team that arrives first in the final leg is awarded a grand prize.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>American Chopper</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on TLC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>American Chopper is a reality television series that airs on Discovery Channel, produced by Pilgrim Films &amp; Television. The series centers on Paul Teutul, Sr. and his son Paul Teutul, Jr. (also known as Paulie and simply Junior, respectively), who manufacture custom motorcycles. Orange County Choppers is in Newburgh, New York. The contrasting attitudes of the two men and their propensity for argument often lead to heated exchanges as they meet unusually short deadlines for building distinctive custom choppers.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>American Horror Story</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>American Pickers</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HISTORY</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>American Pickers is an American reality television series that premiered on January 18, 2010 on History Channel. The series began running concurrently on sister channel Lifetime in December 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ancient Aliens</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on H2</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Ancient Aliens is an American television series that premiered on April 20, 2010 on the History channel. The show has been criticized for presenting disputed pseudoscience.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Anger Management</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name></name>
        <airtime>Airtime: () on </airtime>
        <status> Status: </status>
        <country> Country: </country>
        <runtime> Runtime:  min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>An Idiot Abroad</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on Sky One</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>An Idiot Abroad is a travel documentary television series broadcast on Sky1, as well as a spin-off book published by Canongate Books,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Apprentice (US)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Apprentice is a television franchise which originated in 2004 in the United States. As originally conceived, the show depicted 16 contestants from around the country with various backgrounds competing in an elimination-style competition to become an apprentice to Donald Trump. The winning contestant would have the opportunity to work for Trump as the president of one of his companies for at least one year with an annual salary of $250,000. The Apprentice was developed by British TV producer Mark Burnett, who successfully brought Survivor to the US. Since its premier, the show has spawned many licensed international versions as well as several imitations.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Aqua Teen Hunger Force</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:55:00(US/Eastern) on Adult Swim</airtime>
        <status> Status: TBD/On The Bubble</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
        <description>Aqua Teen Hunger Force (often abbreviated as ATHF or Aqua Teen), later renamed Aqua Unit Patrol Squad 1 (or AUPS1), is an American animated television series shown on Cartoon Network's late night programing block, Adult Swim, as well as Teletoon's Teletoon at Night block and later G4 Canada's ADd block in Canada. It is one of four spin-offs of Adult Swim's Space Ghost Coast to Coast, and as of 2011, the longest running original series on Adult Swim, as well as the only remaining original series continuously airing since the program block launched in 2001. It originally premiered in a block with three other original Williams Street series in December 2000, before Adult Swim officially debuted; the others were Sealab 2021, The Brak Show, and Harvey Birdman, Attorney at Law.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Arrow</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Art Attack</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 10:45:00(GMT+0 +DST) on DiSNEY Junior</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 25 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Assistants</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on TeenNick</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Assistant is a reality television show that parodied other reality shows such as The Apprentice, The Bachelor, The Bachelorette, Survivor, American Idol, and Fear Factor. Its eight episodes originally aired on MTV. It featured comedian Andy Dick's search for a new personal assistant. The beginning of the first episode parodied The Bachelor, with the twelve contestants arriving in limousines, and Dick waiting outside to greet them with his maid and butler. A "rose ceremony" immediately followed, and one contestant was eliminated.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Awake</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Awake (formerly titled REM) is an upcoming American NBC television series starring Jason Isaacs.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Awkward</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Awkward. is an American comedy-drama series which premiered on July 19, 2011 on MTV. The show revolves around the life of 16-year-old Jenna Hamilton (Ashley Rickards), who is struggling with her identity, especially after an accident is misconstrued as a suicide attempt.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Baby Daddy</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Bachelor</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 120 min</runtime>
        <description>A bachelor is an unmarried man.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Bachelorette</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: TBD/On The Bubble</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 120 min</runtime>
        <description>The Bachelorette is a spin-off of the American competitive reality dating game show The Bachelor. In its January 2003 debut on ABC, the first season featured Trista Rehn, the runner-up date from the first season of The Bachelor, offering the opportunity for Rehn to choose a husband among 25 bachelors. The 2004 season of The Bachelorette again took a runner-up from the previous season of The Bachelor. After last airing on February 28, 2005, the series returned to ABC during the spring of 2008, following an absence of three years.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Back to You</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Back to You is an American situation comedy series, which aired on Fox from September 19, 2007 to May 14, 2008. The creators and executive producers were Christopher Lloyd and Steven Levitan, and the director was James Burrows. It was cancelled after one season.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Banshee</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CINEMAX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Being Erica</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Being Erica is a Canadian television comedy-drama series that first aired on January 5, 2009 on CBC.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Benidorm</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on itv</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Benidorm is an award-winning British television comedy-drama that is produced by Tiger Aspect for ITV and written by Derren Litten, co-writer of The Catherine Tate Show, exploiting the working-class stereotype of this popular tourist destination.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Better With You</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Better with You is an American romantic sitcom TV show starring Joanna Garcia Swisher and Jennifer Finnigan. The series aired on Wednesdays at 8:30 pm Eastern/7:30 pm Central on ABC and ran from September 22, 2010 to May 11, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Better Off Ted</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Better Off Ted is an American satirical situation comedy series, created and written by Victor Fresco (known for his other television series Andy Richter Controls the Universe and the short-lived show Life on a Stick), who also serves as the show's Executive Producer. The series premiered on the ABC network on March 18, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Big Bang Theory</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Big Love</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Big Time Rush</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Blandings</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 18:30:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Blue Bloods</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Blue Bloods is an American police procedural/drama series on CBS, filmed on location in New York City. with episodes airing on Fridays at 10:00 PM Eastern and Pacific/9:00 PM Central and Mountain.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Blue Mountain State</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:00:00(US/Eastern) on SPIKE</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Blue Mountain State is an American comedy series that premiered on Spike on January 11, 2010. The series producers include Chris Romano and Eric Falconer and is produced by Lionsgate Television.The series is about a fictional college, Blue Mountain State, in the Midwestern United States and its fictional football team "The Goats". It covers topics of college life, including football, sex, drinking binges, drugs, wild partying, and hazing.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Boardwalk Empire</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Boardwalk Empire is an American television series from cable network HBO, set in Atlantic City, New Jersey, during the Prohibition era. It stars Steve Buscemi as Enoch "Nucky" Thompson. The show was adapted from a book about historical criminal kingpin Enoch "Nucky" Johnson by Nelson Johnson entitled Boardwalk Empire: The Birth, High Times, and Corruption of Atlantic City,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Bold and the Beautiful</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 13:30:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Bold and the Beautiful is an American television soap opera created by William J. Bell and Lee Phillip Bell for CBS Daytime. It premiered on March 23, 1987.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Bones</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Bones is an American crime drama television series that premiered on the Fox Network on September 13, 2005. The show is based on forensic anthropology and forensic archaeology, with each episode focusing on an FBI case file concerning the mystery behind human remains brought by FBI Special Agent Seeley Booth (David Boreanaz) to the forensic anthropologist Dr. Temperance "Bones" Brennan (Emily Deschanel). The rest of the cast includes Michaela Conlin, T. J. Thyne, Eric Millegan, Tamara Taylor, and John Francis Daley.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Boondocks</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:30:00(US/Eastern) on Adult Swim</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Boondocks is an American animated series created by Aaron McGruder on Cartoon Network's late night programing block, Adult Swim, based on McGruder's comic strip of the same name. The Boondocks is a social satire of African American culture and race relations revolving around the lives of the Freeman family: ten-year-old Huey, his younger brother, eight-year-old Riley, and their grandfather, Robert. The series is produced by Rebel Base and has finished airing its third season on Adult Swim. In a 2011 interview, cast member, John Witherspoon announced that the series has been renewed for a fourth season, which will consist of 20 episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Bored to Death</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Boston Legal</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Boston Legal is an American legal dramedy created by David E. Kelley, which was produced in association with 20th Century Fox Television for the ABC. The series aired from October 3, 2004, to December 8, 2008.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Breaking Bad</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on amc</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Breaking Bad is an American television drama series created and produced by Vince Gilligan. The series is broadcast in the United States and Canada on the cable channel AMC, and is a production of Sony Pictures Television. It premiered on January 20, 2008. The fourth season premiered on July 17, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Breakout Kings</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on A&amp;E</airtime>
        <status>; Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Breakout Kings is an American drama television series created by Nick Santora and Matt Olmstead, which airs on the A&amp;E; network. The series premiered on March 6, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Bunheads</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Burn Notice</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on usa network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Burn Notice is an American television series created by Matt Nix. The show stars Jeffrey Donovan, Gabrielle Anwar, Bruce Campbell, Sharon Gless, and, beginning in the fourth season, Coby Bell. The show currently runs in the 9/8c pm slot.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Cake Boss</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on TLC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Cake Boss is an American reality television series, airing on the cable television network TLC. Set at Carlo's Bakery in Hoboken, New Jersey, the show mainly follows Buddy Valastro, his mother, four sisters, and three brothers-in-law, as they operate their business, with a focus on how they make their cakes. However, many episodes of the show have included other events, such as vacations taken by the Valastro family. The show premiered on April 19, 2009, and three additional seasons followed, premiering October 26, 2009, May 31, 2010 (returning in October), and January 31, 2011, respectively.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Californication</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Californication is an American comedy-drama that premiered on Showtime on August 13, 2007. The show was created by Tom Kapinos. The protagonist, Hank Moody (David Duchovny), is a troubled novelist whose move to California, coupled with his writer's block, complicates his relationships with his longtime girlfriend Karen (Natascha McElhone) and daughter Becca (Madeleine Martin). Californication's other main characters are Charlie Runkle (Evan Handler), Marcy Runkle (Pamela Adlon), and Mia Lewis (Madeline Zima). The show has been nominated and won several awards, including winning one Emmy Award (nominated for two others) and one Golden Globe Award (nominated for three others). Californication has aired for four complete seasons. Due to strong ratings for the third season premiere, Showtime renewed the show early for a fourth season. and is set to premiere on January 8, 2012.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Camelot</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on starz</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Camelot is an Irish/Canadian historical-fantasy-drama television series which premiered on April 1, 2011. It was co-produced by the Starz cable network and GK-TV which began production during the summer of 2010. The series, based on the Arthurian legend, was produced by Graham King, Morgan O'Sullivan and Michael Hirst.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Camp</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Caprica</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Caprica is a science fiction drama television series. It is a spin-off prequel of the re-imagined Battlestar Galactica, taking place about 58 years prior to the events of Battlestar Galactica. Caprica shows how humanity first created the robotic Cylons who would later plot to destroy humans in retaliation for their enslavement. Among Caprica's main characters are the father and uncle of Commander William Adama from the re-imagined Battlestar Galactica.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Castle (2009)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Chicago Fire</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Chuck</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Chuck is an action-comedy/spy-drama television program from the United States created by Josh Schwartz and Chris Fedak. The series is about an "average computer-whiz-next-door" named Chuck, played by Zachary Levi, who receives an encoded e-mail from an old college friend now working for the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA); the message embeds the only remaining copy of the United States' greatest spy secrets into Chuck's brain.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Cleveland Show</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Cleveland Show is an American animated television series that premiered on September 27, 2009, as a part of the "Animation Domination" lineup on Fox in the United States. The series was created by Seth MacFarlane, Mike Henry, and Richard Appel as a spin-off from Family Guy, which was also created by MacFarlane.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Code Monkeys</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on G4</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The Colbert Report</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:30:00(US/Eastern) on Comedy Central</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Cold Case</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Cold case may refer to:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Colony</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on SBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: AU</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Colony is a reality television series that is produced by the Discovery Channel. The program follows a group of people who might survive in a post-apocalyptic environment.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Community</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Cops</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on SPIKE</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>COPS is an American documentary/reality television series that follows police officers, constables, and sheriff's deputies during patrols and other police activities. It is one of the longest-running television programs in the United States and in May 2011 became longest-running show on Fox with the announcement that America's Most Wanted was being canceled after 23 years.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Corner Gas</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on CTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Corner Gas is a Canadian television sitcom created by Brent Butt. The series ran for six seasons from 2004 to 2009. Re-runs still air on CTV and The Comedy Network in Canada; it formerly aired on WGN America in the United States.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Coronation Street</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(Great Britain) on itv</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Coronation Street is a long-running British soap opera set in Weatherfield, a fictional town based on Salford in North West England. Created by Tony Warren, Coronation Street was first broadcast on 9 December 1960. It is produced by Granada Television (now known as ITV Studios) and has been filmed at their Manchester Studios since its inception. It has since been shown in all regions of ITV almost throughout its existence.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Cougar Town</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on tbs</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Cougar Town is an American television sitcom that premiered on ABC on September 23, 2009. The series focuses on a recently divorced woman in her forties facing the often humorous challenges, pitfalls and rewards of life's next chapter, along with her son, ex-husband, and friends who together make up her dysfunctional, but supportive and caring extended family.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Covert Affairs</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on usa network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Covert Affairs is a USA Network television series starring Piper Perabo and Christopher Gorham. The one-hour drama premiered on Tuesday, July 13, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Criminal Minds</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Criminal Minds is an American police procedural drama that premiered September 22, 2005, on CBS. The series follows a team of profilers from the FBI's Behavioral Analysis Unit (BAU) based in Quantico, Virginia. The BAU is part of the FBI National Center for the Analysis of Violent Crime.Criminal Minds differs from many procedural dramas by focusing on the criminal rather than the crime itself. The show is produced by The Mark Gordon Company in association with CBS Television Studios and ABC Studios.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Crusoe</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Crusoe is a television adventure drama (with comedic elements) based loosely on the novel Robinson Crusoe by Daniel Defoe. The series' 13 episodes aired on NBC during the first half of the 2008-2009 television season. It follows the adventures of Robinson Crusoe: a man who has been shipwrecked on an island for six years and is desperate to return home to his wife and children. His lone companion is Friday, a native whom Crusoe rescued and taught English.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Curb Your Enthusiasm</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: TBD/On The Bubble</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Curb Your Enthusiasm is an American comedy television series produced and broadcast by HBO, which premiered on October 15, 2000. As of 2011, it has completed 80 episodes over eight seasons. The series was created by Seinfeld co-creator Larry David, who stars as a fictionalized version of himself. The series follows David in his life as a semi-retired television writer and producer in Los Angeles and later New York City. Also starring is Cheryl Hines as David's wife Cheryl, Jeff Garlin as David's manager Jeff, and Susie Essman as Jeff's wife Susie. Curb often features guest stars, and some of these appearances are by celebrities playing themselves.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Daily Show</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:00:00(US/Eastern) on Comedy Central</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Daily Show (called The Daily Show with Jon Stewart since 1999), is an American late night satirical television program airing each Monday through Thursday on Comedy Central. The half-hour long show premiered on July 21, 1996, and was hosted by Craig Kilborn until December 1998. Jon Stewart took over as host in January 1999, making the show more strongly focused on politics and the national media, in contrast with the pop culture focus during Kilborn's tenure. It is currently the longest running program on Comedy Central, and has won sixteen Emmy Awards.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Damages</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on AUDIENCE NETWORK</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Damages is an American television drama series created by the writing and production trio of Daniel Zelman and brothers Glenn and Todd A. Kessler (collectively known as KZK). It is broadcast in the United States on the DirecTV channel Audience Network after originally airing on FX and is produced by the creators' own production company, KZK Productions. It premiered on July 24, 2007.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dark Blue</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on TNT</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dark Blue was an action/drama television series which premiered on TNT on July 15, 2009, at 10 pm (9 pm Central). It ended its run on September 15, 2010. The series is set in Los Angeles, California. It revolves around Carter Shaw (Dylan McDermott), the leader of an undercover unit. He is an officer who has dedicated his life to taking down the worst criminals in L.A., and this dedication has cost him his marriage. His team includes Ty Curtis, a newlywed who struggles between his job and his new life; Dean Bendis, an officer who is so deep in his undercover role that his team is no longer sure which side he is on; and Jaimie Allen, a green patrol cop recruited into the undercover unit because of her dark past and criminal skills.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Days of our Lives</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 13:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Days of our Lives is a daytime soap opera broadcast on the NBC television network. It is one of the longest running scripted television programs in the world, airing nearly every weekday in the United States since November 8, 1965. It also rebroadcasts on SOAPnet with the earlier same day's broadcast airing weekdays at 10 a.m. and the most recent episode airing weeknights at 6 and 11 p.m. (ET/PT). The series was created by husband-and-wife team Ted Corday and Betty Corday. Irna Phillips was a story editor for Days of Our Lives and many of the first stories were also written by William J. Bell. The series expanded from 30 minutes to a full hour on April 21, 1975.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Death In Paradise</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT+0 +DST) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Defying Gravity</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Defying Gravity is a multi-nationally produced space travel television science fiction drama series, first aired on August 2, 2009 on ABC and CTV and canceled in the autumn of 2009. Set in the year 2052, the series follows eight astronauts (four women and four men) from four countries on a six-year space mission through the Solar System,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Desperate Housewives</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Desperate Housewives is an American television comedy-drama series created by Marc Cherry and produced by ABC Studios and Cherry Productions. Executive producer Cherry serves as Showrunner. Other executive producers since the fourth season include Marc Cherry, Bob Daily, George W. Perkins, John Pardee and Joey Murphy, David Grossman, Larry Shaw and Sabrina Wind.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dexter</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dexter is an American television drama series that centers on Dexter Morgan (Michael C. Hall), a bloodstain pattern analyst for the Miami Metro Police Department who moonlights as a serial killer. The show debuted on October 1, 2006, on Showtime and the fifth season ended on December 12, 2010. As of December 2, 2010, the show has been renewed for a sixth season. Set in Miami, the show's first season was largely based on the novel Darkly Dreaming Dexter by Jeff Lindsay, the first of his series of Dexter novels. Subsequent seasons have evolved independently of Lindsay's works. It was adapted for television by screenwriter James Manos, Jr., who wrote the first episode.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dharma &amp; Greg</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dirt</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dirt (styled d!rt for logos) is an American television serial broadcast on the FX network. It premiered on January 2, 2007 and starred Courteney Cox as Lucy Spiller, the editor-in-chief of the first-of-its-kind "glossy tabloid" magazine DirtNow, which was previously two separate publications: drrt (a tabloid) and Now (a glossy magazine with a more respectable reputation.).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dirty Jobs</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Discovery Channel</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dirty Jobs is a program on the Discovery Channel, produced by Pilgrim Films &amp; Television, in which host Mike Rowe is shown performing difficult, strange, disgusting, or messy occupational duties alongside the typical employees. The show premiered with two pilot episodes in November 2003. It returned as a series on July 26, 2005.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dirty Sexy Money</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dirty Sexy Money is an American prime time drama series created by Craig Wright, which ran on the ABC from September 26, 2007 to August 8, 2009. The series was produced by ABC Studios, Bad Hat Harry Productions, Berlanti Television and Gross Entertainment. Wright serves as an executive producer alongside Greg Berlanti, Bryan Singer, Matthew Gross, Peter Horton and Josh Reims, with Melissa Berman producing.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Dollhouse</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Dollhouse is an American science fiction television series created by writer and director Joss Whedon under Mutant Enemy Productions. It premiered on February 13, 2009, on the Fox network and was officially cancelled on November 11, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Downton Abbey</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on itv</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Downton Abbey is a British television period drama series, produced by British media company Carnival Films for the ITV network. The series is set during the Edwardian era in the fictional estate of Downton, Yorkshire, and features an ensemble cast led by British actors Hugh Bonneville and Maggie Smith. It was created and principally written by actor and writer Julian Fellowes, and first aired on the ITV1 network on 26 September 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Drop Dead Diva</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Lifetime</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Drop Dead Diva is an American legal comedy-drama/fantasy television series that debuted on Lifetime on July 12, 2009. The hour-long series, which was created by Josh Berman, is produced by Sony Pictures Television. The series stars Brooke Elliott as Jane, a plus size woman whose body is inhabited by the soul of a fashion model.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>EastEnders</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Eastwick</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Eastwick is a 2009 screwball comedy series based on John Updike's novel, The Witches of Eastwick. The series was developed by Maggie Friedman, and starred Paul Gross as the infamous Darryl Van Horne, alongside Jaime Ray Newman , Lindsay Price, and Rebecca Romijn as the eponymous witches.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Elementary</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Eli Stone</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Eli Stone is an American TV series, and also the name of the title character.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Emmerdale</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:00:00(Great Britain) on ITV1</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Emmerdale, (known as Emmerdale Farm until 1989) is a long-running British soap opera set in Emmerdale (known as Beckindale until 1994), a fictional village in the Yorkshire Dales. Created by Kevin Laffan, Emmerdale was first broadcast on 16 October 1972. It is produced by Yorkshire Television, (now known as ITV Studios), and has been filmed at their Yorkshire Studios since its inception. It has since been shown in all regions of ITV almost throughout its existence. It is the United Kingdom's second oldest soap opera.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Endgame</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on SHOWCASE</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Endgame is a Canadian drama television series that premiered on the Showcase Television network on Monday, March 14, 2011. The series is developed and produced by Thunderbird Films. The series follows former World Chess Champion Arkady Balagan (Shawn Doyle), a genius who uses his analytical skills to solve crimes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Entourage</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Entourage is an American comedy-drama television series that premiered on HBO on July 18, 2004 and concluded on September 11, 2011, after eight seasons. The series was created by and largely written by Doug Ellin and chronicles the acting career of Vincent Chase, a young A-list movie star, and his childhood friends from Queens, New York City, as they navigate the unfamiliar terrain of Los Angeles, California.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Episodes</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Episodes is a British/American television sitcom serial created by David Crane and Jeffrey Klarik and produced by Hat Trick Productions.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>ER</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>ER is an American medical drama television series created by novelist Michael Crichton that aired on NBC from September 19, 1994 to April 2, 2009. It was produced by Constant c Productions and Amblin Entertainment, in association with Warner Bros. Television. It is set primarily in the emergency room (ER) of fictional County General Hospital in Chicago, Illinois. The show ran for 15 seasons, becoming the longest-running primetime medical drama in American television history. It won 23 Emmy Awards, including the 1996 Outstanding Drama Series award. It received 124 Emmy nominations, which makes it the most nominated drama program in history.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Eternal Law</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT+0 +DST) on itv</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Eureka</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Eureka (stylized as EUReKA) is an American science fiction television series that premiered on Syfy on July 18, 2006. Since then four seasons have aired, and a fifth is currently being filmed. The second half of season 4 began on SyFy on July 11, 2011 and ended on September 19, 2011. The show is set in a fictional town called Eureka, Oregon, in the Pacific Northwest inhabited almost entirely by geniuses and scientists. Nearly everyone in Eureka works for Global Dynamics, a huge advanced research facility responsible for the development of all major technological breakthroughs in the last 50 years. Each episode features a mysterious accidental or intentional misuse of technology, which the town Sheriff Jack Carter then solves with the help of town scientists. Each season also features a larger story arc that concerns a particular major event or item.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Event</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Everybody Hates Chris</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on The CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Everybody Hates Chris is an American sitcom inspired by the teenage experiences of comedian Chris Rock (who is also the narrator), while growing up in the Bedford-Stuyvesant neighborhood of Brooklyn, New York (often referred to in the show as Bed-Stuy). The show is set from 1982 to 1987; however, Rock himself was a teenager during years 1978-1983. Chris Rock grew up with a boy named Kenny Montero who he has often referred to as the inspiration for a lot of the episodes. In many interviews, Rock has described Kenny as the reason he got into comedy in the first place. The title of the show parodies the CBS sitcom Everybody Loves Raymond. Rock stated "Everybody Loves Raymond but Everybody Hates Chris!". The show's lead actors are Tyler James Williams, Terry Crews, Tichina Arnold, Tequan Richmond, Imani Hakim, and Vincent Martella.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Enlightened</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Enlightened is an upcoming American television series starring Laura Dern. The first season, which is set to premiere in 2011 on HBO, will consist of 10 episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
    <show>
        <name>Falling Skies</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Turner Network Television</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Falling Skies is an American science fiction dramatic television series created by Robert Rodat and produced by Steven Spielberg. The series picks up six months into a world devastated by an alien invasion. Tom Mason, a former Boston University history professor, becomes the second-in-command of the 2nd Massachusetts Militia Regiment, a group of civilians and fighters fleeing post-apocalyptic Boston.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Family Guy</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Family Guy is an American animated television series created by Seth MacFarlane for the Fox Broadcasting Company. The series centers on the Griffins, a dysfunctional family consisting of parents Peter and Lois; their children Meg, Chris, and Stewie; and their anthropomorphic pet dog Brian. The show is set in the fictional city of Quahog, Rhode Island, and exhibits much of its humor in the form of cutaway gags that often lampoon American culture.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Fear Itself</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Fear Itself was a horror/suspense anthology television series shot in the city of Edmonton, Alberta, Canada, with some additional shooting in the city of St. Albert and the town of Devon, Alberta. It began airing on June 5, 2008 on NBC.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>FlashForward</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>FlashForward is an American television series, adapted for TV by Brannon Braga and David S. Goyer, which aired on ABC between September 24, 2009 and May 27, 2010. It is based on the 1999 novel Flashforward by Canadian science fiction writer Robert J. Sawyer. The series was cancelled in May 2010. The series revolves around the lives of several people as a mysterious event causes nearly everyone on the planet to simultaneously lose consciousness for two minutes and seventeen seconds on October 6, 2009. During this "blackout", people see what appear to be visions of their lives on April 29, 2010, a global "flashforward".</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Flashpoint</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Flashpoint is a Canadian police drama television series that debuted on July 11, 2008, on CTV in Canada and ran on CBS in the United States for its first three and a half seasons. In 2011, Ion Television began airing new episodes of the series in the United States. The series has been broadcast on the Canadian French-language network V (formerly known as TQS) in Quebec since March 9, 2009. The show was created by Mark Ellis and Stephanie Morgenstern and stars Hugh Dillon, Amy Jo Johnson, David Paetkau and Enrico Colantoni. It was announced January 25, 2011 that Ion Television had acquired all rights to the show and to continue production in-house.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Flight of the Conchords</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Flight of the Conchords is an American television comedy series that debuted on HBO on June 17, 2007. The show follows the adventures of Flight of the Conchords, a two-man band from New Zealand, as its members seek fame and success in New York City. The show stars the real-life duo, Jemaine Clement and Bret McKenzie, who play fictionalized versions of themselves. A second season was announced on August 17, 2007, and premiered on January 18 2009. On December 11, 2009, the duo confirmed that the series would not return for a third season.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Flipping Out</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Bravo</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Flipping Out is a reality television series that debuted on July 31, 2007 on Bravo in the United States and HGTV in Canada. Subsequently, it debuted on cable network Arena in Australia on September 4, 2009. For the first season it also re-aired on sister network CNBC. The show is centered on designer Jeff Lewis in Los Angeles, California, his entourage that consists of his project manager Jenni, housekeeper Zoila, business manager and boyfriend Gage and his other assistant(s) and helper(s).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Forgotten (2009)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Forgotten is a television series which premiered on September 22, 2009 on ABC. On November 9, 2009, ABC ordered five additional episodes of the series, bringing the first season's total to eighteen episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Fresh Meat</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT+0 +DST) on Channel 4</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 50 min</runtime>
        <description>Fresh Meat is a British sitcom writen by Jesse Armstrong and Sam Bain for Channel 4. It first aired on 21st September 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Friday Night Lights</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on AUDIENCE NETWORK</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Friday Night Lights is an American sports drama television series adapted by Peter Berg, Brian Grazer and David Nevins from a book and film of the same name. The series details events surrounding a high school football team based in fictional Dillon, Texas, with particular focus given to team coach Eric Taylor (Kyle Chandler) and his family. The show uses this small town backdrop to address many issues facing contemporary American culture, including school funding, racism, drugs, abortion, and lack of economic opportunities.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Fringe</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Fringe is an American science fiction television series created by J. J. Abrams, Alex Kurtzman and Roberto Orci. The series follows a Federal Bureau of Investigation "Fringe Division" team based in Boston, Massachusetts under the supervision of Homeland Security. The team uses unorthodox "fringe" science and FBI investigative techniques to investigate a series of unexplained, often ghastly occurrences, which are related to mysteries surrounding a parallel universe. The show has been described as a hybrid of The X-Files, Altered States, The Twilight Zone and Dark Angel.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Futurama</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on Comedy Central</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Futurama is an American animated science fiction sitcom created by Matt Groening and developed by Groening and David X. Cohen for the Fox Broadcasting Company. The series follows the adventures of a late 20th-century New York City pizza delivery boy, Philip J. Fry, who, after being unwittingly cryogenically frozen for one thousand years, finds employment at Planet Express, an interplanetary delivery company in the retro-futuristic 31st century. The series was envisioned by Groening in the 1990s while working on The Simpsons, later bringing Cohen aboard to develop storylines and characters to pitch the show to Fox.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Game of Thrones</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The Gates</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Gates is an American supernatural The show was canceled after its first season due to its poor ratings.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ghost Whisperer</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Ghost Whisperer is an American television supernatural drama, which ran on CBS from September 23, 2005 to May 21, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Girls</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Glades</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on A&amp;E</airtime>
        <status>; Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Glades is an A&amp;E; Network drama television series starring Matt Passmore. The one-hour drama premiered on Sunday, July 11, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Glee</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Glee is an American musical comedy-drama television series that airs on Fox in the United States, and on Global and Fox Canada in Canada. It touches on the high school glee club New Directions competing on the show choir competition circuit, while its members deal with relationships, sexuality and social issues. The initial main cast encompassed club director and Spanish teacher Will Schuester (Matthew Morrison), cheerleading coach Sue Sylvester (Jane Lynch), guidance counselor Emma Pillsbury (Jayma Mays), Will's wife Terri (Jessalyn Gilsig), and eight club members played by Dianna Agron, Chris Colfer, Kevin McHale, Lea Michele, Cory Monteith, Amber Riley, Mark Salling and Jenna Ushkowitz. For the second season, formerly recurring cast members Mike O'Malley, Heather Morris and Naya Rivera were promoted to the main cast. For the third season, Harry Shum, Jr. and Darren Criss were promoted from recurring to the main cast, and both Gilsig and O'Malley were removed from star billing, though the latter will again be in the recurring guest cast.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Glee Project</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on oxygen</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Glee Project is an American reality television series from Oxygen. It serves as an audition for the FOX TV series Glee. Although originally planned to begin broadcasting in late May 2011, The Glee Project premiered on June 12, 2011. In Canada, the series began airing on Slice on June 26, 2011 with a two hour extended premiere where the first hour showed the audition process and selection of the Top 12. In the UK, the series began airing on Sky One on July 14, 2011 with a two hour extended premiere where the first hour showed the audition process and selection of the Top 12.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Go On</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Good Luck Charlie</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Good Luck Charlie is an original Disney Channel television sitcom, which premiered April 4, 2010. The series was created by Phil Baker and Drew Vaupen, who wanted to create a program that would appeal to entire families, as opposed to children only. It revolves around a Denver family, the Duncans, as they try to adjust to the birth of their fourth child, Charlotte "Charlie" Duncan (Mia Talerico). In each episode, Teddy Duncan (Bridgit Mendler) creates a video diary containing advice for Charlie about their family and life as a teenager. Teddy tries to show Charlie what she might go through when she is older in the video diaries for future reference.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Good Wife</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Good Wife is an American legal drama that premiered on CBS on September 22, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Gossip Girl</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Gossip Girl is an American teen drama television series based on the book series of the same name written by Cecily von Ziegesar. The series was created by Josh Schwartz and Stephanie Savage, and premiered on The CW on September 19, 2007. Narrated by the omniscient yet unseen blogger "Gossip Girl", voiced by Kristen Bell, the series revolves around the lives of privileged young adults on Manhattan's Upper East Side in New York City.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Gravity Falls</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>GREEK</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Grimm</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Grimm is an upcoming American fantasy/mystery/crime drama series set to debut on NBC on October 21, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hannah Montana</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Hannah Montana is an American television series, which debuted on March 24, 2006 on Disney Channel, and also airs Saturday mornings on ABC as part of the ABC Kids block. As of July 21, 2011, Hannah Montana is no longer aired in reruns on Disney Channel in the 1AM &amp; 1:30AM Eastern Standard Time slot as it has been replaced by Good Luck Charlie. As ABC Kids was be replaced by Litton's Weekend Adventure starting September 3, 2011, this leaves Hannah Montana's final airing to be August 27, 2011 on ABC Kids. However, Hannah Montana: The Movie still airs regularly on Disney Channel.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Happy Endings</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Happy Endings is an American television series for the ABC network. The single-camera ensemble comedy premiered on April 13, 2011, as a midseason replacement,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Hard Times of RJ Berger</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Hard Times of RJ Berger is a United States television comedy series created by David Katzenberg and Seth Grahame-Smith for MTV. The show's central character is RJ Berger (Paul Iacono) an unpopular sophomore at the fictional Pinkerton High School in Ohio who has an exceptionally large penis. Berger's two best friends are Miles Jenner (Jareb Dauplaise), whose ambitions for popularity cause him to clash with Berger, and goth girl Lily Miran (Kara Taitz), who has been lusting after Berger for several years. Berger's love interest is Jenny Swanson (Amber Lancaster), a cheerleader who is involved with Max Owens (Jayson Blair), a popular jock and bully. The show is presented as a coming of age story and has been described by Katzenberg and Grahame-Smith as a blend of the television series The Wonder Years and the film Superbad. The pilot episode premiered on June 6, 2010, and the first season of 12 episodes concluded August 23, 2010. MTV renewed the series for a second season, which premiered on March 24, 2011. Series creator Seth Grahame-Smith confirmed via Twitter in August 2011 that the series is canceled.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hart Of Dixie</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Hart of Dixie is an upcoming American medical drama television series. On May 17, 2011, The CW officially picked up the pilot to series.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Haven</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Haven is a supernatural drama television series loosely based on the Stephen King novel The Colorado Kid. The show, filmed on the South Shore of Nova Scotia, Canada, is an American/Canadian co-production. The one-hour drama premiered on July 9, 2010, on Syfy.WWE wrestler Edge has a re-occuring role on show.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hawthorne</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Turner Network Television</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Hawthorne (sometimes stylized HawthoRNe) was an hour-long medical drama on the TNT television network starring Jada Pinkett Smith and Michael Vartan. It premiered on June 16, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hell on Wheels</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on AMC</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Hell on Wheels is an upcoming American dramatic television series created and produced by Joe and Tony Gayton. Set in the 1865, the series stars Anson Mount as Cullen Bohannon, a former Confederate soldier who is determined to exact revenge on the Union soldiers who murdered his wife.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hellcats</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Hellcats is an American cheerleading comedy-drama television series that originally aired on The CW in the United States from September 8, 2010 to May 17, 2011. Based on the book Cheer: Inside the Secret World of College Cheerleaders by journalist Kate Torgovnick, the series focuses in the lives of college cheerleaders, mainly Marti Perkins (Aly Michalka), a pre-law college student who has to join the cheerleading team, the Hellcats, in order to get the athletic scholarship she needs. The main cast also includes Ashley Tisdale, Robbie Jones, Heather Hemmens, Matt Barr, Gail O'Grady and Sharon Leal.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Heroes</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Heroes is an American science fiction television drama series created by Tim Kring that appeared on NBC for four seasons from September 25, 2006 through February 8, 2010. The series tells the stories of ordinary people who discover superhuman abilities, and how these abilities take effect in the characters' lives. The series emulates the aesthetic style and storytelling of American comic books, using short, multi-episode story arcs that build upon a larger, more encompassing arc.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Hills</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Hills is an MTV television series that premiered on May 31, 2006. The show uses a reality television format, following the personal lives of several young adults living in Los Angeles, California. The series originally followed the personal life of former Laguna Beach star Lauren Conrad and her friends' new lives in Los Angeles. After five seasons, Conrad chose to leave the series, and was replaced by another former Laguna Beach star, Kristin Cavallari, beginning in the second half of season five. Cavallari signed on for two additional seasons following the fifth.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hollywood Heights</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on nick@nite</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Homeland</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Hot In Cleveland</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on TVland</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Hot in Cleveland is an American sitcom on TV Land starring Valerie Bertinelli, Jane Leeves, Wendie Malick and Betty White. The series, which is TV Land's first original scripted series, premiered on June 16, 2010, and was TV Land's highest rated telecast in the cable network's 14-year history. The series premiered June 16, 2010, and was picked up for ten episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>House</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>House of Anubis</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>House of Anubis is a jointly American/British/Belgian produced teen mystery/drama television show based on the Belgian/Dutch television series Het Huis Anubis. The series was created by Hans Bourlon &amp; Gert Verhulst and premiered on Nickelodeon on New Year's Day 2011 in the United States and on 25 February 2011 in the United Kingdom. The series is the first Nickelodeon series to be filmed overseas, the first soap opera created by Nickelodeon and the channel's first soap opera aimed at children and teenagers (sixth in Latin America).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>House of Lies</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Showtime</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>How I Met Your Mother</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Hung</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Hung is a comedy-drama series, which premiered on HBO on June 28, 2009. The series was created by Dmitry Lipkin and Colette Burson and stars Thomas Jane as Ray Drecker, a struggling suburban Detroit high school basketball coach who resorts to male prostitution. The second season premiered on June 27, 2010 and concluded its 10 episode run on September 12, 2010. On September 2, 2010 it was announced that HBO had ordered Hung for a third season consisting of 10 episodes set to premiere on October 2, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Hustle</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>iCarly</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>iCarly is an American sitcom that focuses on a girl named Carly Shay who creates her own web show called iCarly with her best friends Sam and Freddie. The series was created by Dan Schneider, who also serves as executive producer. It stars Miranda Cosgrove as Carly, Jennette McCurdy as Sam, Nathan Kress as Freddie, Jerry Trainor as Spencer, and Noah Munck as Gibby. The show is taped at Nickelodeon On Sunset in Hollywood, California.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>In The Night Garden</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(Great Britain) on Cbeebies</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>In the Night Garden... (usually presented with an ellipsis) is a BBC children's television series, aimed at children aged Two to Four. It was produced by Andrew Davenport and Anne Wood, both of whom co-created Teletubbies. The programme is narrated by Derek Jacobi. It is filmed mostly in live action, and features a mix of actors in costumes, plus puppetry and computer animation.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Instant Mom</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>In Treatment</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The IT Crowd</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Channel 4</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Jane By Design</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>A list of television shows, programs or networks where the setting takes place in, or revolves around, the world of beauty and fashion in general (beautification, magazines, styles, imaging, modeling, makeovers, trends, etc.).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Jericho</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Jericho is an American action/drama series that centers on the residents of the fictional town of Jericho, Kansas, in the aftermath of nuclear attacks on 23 major cities in the contiguous United States. Produced by CBS Paramount Network Television, with executive producers Jon Turteltaub, Stephen Chbosky, and Carol Barbee, the show was broadcast in more than 30 countries.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Jersey Shore</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Jersey Shore is an American reality television series that premiered on MTV on December 3, 2009 in the United States. The series follows the lives of eight housemates spending their summer at the Jersey Shore. Season 2 followed the cast escaping the cold northeast winter to Miami Beach, with Season 3 returning to the Jersey Shore. The fourth season, filmed in Italy, premiered on August 4, 2011. MTV confirmed in June 2011 that Season 5 will return to Seaside Heights.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>JONAS</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on Disney Channel</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Jonas L.A. (previously titled Jonas) is a Disney Channel Original Series created by Michael Curtis and Roger Schulman, starring the Jonas Brothers. The pilot was filmed in September 2008, first-run episodes aired on.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Justified</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Justified is an American television drama series created by Graham Yost. It is based on Elmore Leonard's novels Pronto and Riding the Rap and his short story "Fire in the Hole".</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Keeping Up with the Kardashians</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on E!</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Keeping Up with the Kardashians is an American reality television series airing on E! that premiered on October 14, 2007. The series focuses on the personal and professional lives of the members of the Kardashian/Jenner family.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Killing</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Netflix</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Killing is an American crime drama television series based on the Danish television series with the same English title, but known as Forbrydelsen (The Crime) in Danish. The American version was developed by Veena Sud and produced by Fox Television Studios and Fuse Entertainment. The series' first season, consisting of 13 hour-long episodes, premiered on the cable channel AMC on April 3, 2011, with a two-hour premiere.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>King of the Hill</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>King of the Hill (also known as Hank of the Hill in some parts of Western Europe) is an American animated dramedy series created by Mike Judge and Greg Daniels, that ran from January 12, 1997, to May 6, 2010, on the FOX network. It centers on the Hills, a working-class Methodist family in the fictional small town of Arlen, Texas. It attempts to retain a realistic approach, seeking humor in the conventional and mundane aspects of everyday life while dealing with comical issues.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Kourtney and Khloe Take Miami</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on E!</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Kourtney and Kim Take New York</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on E!</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Kourtney and Kim Take New York is an American reality television series, produced by Ryan Seacrest, that debuted on E! in the United States and Canada on January 23, 2011. In August 2011 it was announced that a second season will be made so Kim could be close to her husband.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Kyle XY</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Kyle XY is an American television series with a science fiction premise and mystery-drama style. The central character is a teenage boy (Matt Dallas) who awakens naked in a forest outside Seattle, Washington, with no more knowledge or abilities than a newborn. He is taken in by a family and given the name Kyle. The series follows Kyle as he tries to solve the puzzles of who he is and why he has no memory before that day. Just as strange, he lacks a belly-button. Although set in present-day Seattle, the series was filmed in the Vancouver, British Columbia, area.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The L Word</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Showtime</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The L Word is an American co-production television drama series originally shown on Showtime portraying the lives of a group of lesbian, bisexual, and transgender people and their friends, family and lovers in the trendy Greater Los Angeles, California city of West Hollywood. The show ran from 2004 to 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Lab Rats</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(Great Britain) on BBC TWO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Next episode airs in:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Las Vegas</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Las Vegas is an American television series that was broadcast by NBC from September 22, 2003 to February 15, 2008. The show focuses on a team of people working at the ficticional Montecito Resort &amp; Casino dealing with issues that arise within the working environment, ranging from valet parking and restaurant management to casino security. The series originally aired on Monday nights, though NBC later moved the series to Friday nights first to 9 PM Eastern/8 PM Central and then to 10 PM Eastern/9 PM Central. The show is currently in syndication and airs in the United States (on TNT).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Late Night with Jimmy Fallon</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 00:35:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Late Night with Jimmy Fallon is an American late-night talk show hosted by Jimmy Fallon on NBC. The show premiered on March 2, 2009, as the third incarnation of the Late Night franchise originated by David Letterman.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Late Show with David Letterman</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:35:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>David Michael Letterman (born April 12, 1947) is an American television host and comedian.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Legend of Korra</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Legend of the Seeker</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syndicated</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Legend of the Seeker is a television series based on The Sword of Truth novels by Terry Goodkind. Distributed in U.S. by Disney-ABC Domestic Television, ABC Studios produced the series, which was its first foray into broadcast syndication, with Sam Raimi, Robert Tapert, Joshua Donen, Ned Nalle and Kenneth Biller serving as executive producers. The show premiered on November 1, 2008 and ran for two seasons before its cancellation in 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Leverage</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Turner Network Television</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Leverage is an American television drama series on TNT that premiered in December 2008. The series is produced by director/executive producer Dean Devlin's production company Electric Television. Leverage follows a five-person team: a thief, a grifter, a hacker and a retrieval specialist, headed up by former insurance investigator Nathan Ford, who use their skills to right corporate and governmental injustices inflicted on ordinary citizens.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Lie to Me</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Lie to Me is an American television series that originally ran on the Fox network from January 21, 2009 to January 31, 2011. In the show, Dr. Cal Lightman (Tim Roth) and his colleagues in The Lightman Group accept assignments from third parties (commonly local and federal law enforcement), and assist in investigations, reaching the truth through applied psychology: interpreting microexpressions, through the Facial Action Coding System, and body language.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Life (US)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Life is a characteristic that distinguishes objects that have self-sustaining biological processes from those which do not.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Little Britain USA</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Little Britain USA, an American television series, originated as a spin-off of the British BBC's Little Britain show.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Little Mosque on the Prairie</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on CBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: CA</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Little Mosque on the Prairie is a Canadian sitcom on CBC, created by Zarqa Nawaz and produced by WestWind Pictures. It is filmed in Toronto, Ontario and Indian Head, Saskatchewan. The series was selected and showcased at the 2009 Dawn Breakers International Film Festival in Zurich.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Longmire</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on A&amp;E</airtime>
        <status>; Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Longmire is an upcoming A&amp;E; Network drama television series set to premiere on June 3, 2012 on A&amp;E.; The series was created by John Coveny and Hunt Baldwin and is based on the "Longmire" series of mystery novels series written by best-selling author Craig Johnson.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Lost</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Lost is an American television series that originally aired on ABC from September 22, 2004 to May 23, 2010, consisting of six seasons. Lost is a drama series that follows the survivors of the crash of a commercial passenger jet flying between Sydney and Los Angeles, on a mysterious tropical island somewhere in the South Pacific Ocean. The story is told in a heavily serialized manner. Episodes typically feature a primary storyline on the island, as well as a secondary storyline from another point in a character's life.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Louie</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Louie is an American comedy television series on the FX network that began airing in 2010. It is written, directed, edited and produced by the show's creator, stand-up comedian Louis C.K., who stars as a fictionalized version of himself, a comedian and newly divorced father raising his two daughters in New York City. The show has a loose format atypical for television comedy series, consisting of largely unconnected storylines and segments (described as "extended vignettes") that revolve around Louie's life, punctuated by live stand-up performances.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Luther</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Luther is a British psychological crime drama television series starring Idris Elba as the title character Detective Chief Inspector John Luther. A first series of six episodes was broadcast on BBC One from 4 May to 8 June 2010. The second series of four episodes was shown on BBC One in summer 2011. During the Edinburgh TV Festival, BBC One controller Danny Cohen announced there will be a third season as well.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Lying Game</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Lying Game is an American drama television series produced by Alloy Entertainment and Warner Horizon Television for ABC Family.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Mad</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
        <description>MADtv is an American sketch comedy television series. It licensed the name and logo of Mad, but otherwise had no connection with the humor magazine outside the animated Spy vs. Spy and Don Martin cartoon shorts and images of Alfred E. Neuman that the show featured during the late 1990s. Its first TV broadcast was on October 14, 1995. The one-hour show aired Saturday nights on Fox and is in syndication on Comedy Central. In Australia the show screens on satellite and cable TV channel The Comedy Channel and in late-night timeslots on free-to-air broadcaster the Nine Network Australia and its affiliates.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Mad Men</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on amc</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Mad Men is an American dramatic television series created and produced by Matthew Weiner. The episodes are premiered on Sunday evenings on the American cable network AMC and are produced by Lionsgate Television. It premiered on July 19, 2007, and completed its fourth season on October 17, 2010. Each season has consisted of 13 episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Make It or Break It</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Make It or Break It is an American television drama series that focuses on the lives of teen gymnasts who strive to make it to the Olympic Games. It premiered on ABC Family on June 22, 2009, with 2.5 million viewers.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Me And My Monsters</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 08:00:00(Great Britain) on CBBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Next episode airs in:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Medium</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Medium is an American television drama series that premiered on NBC on January 3, 2005, and ended on CBS on January 21, 2011. Themed on supernatural gifts, its lead character, Allison DuBois (played by Patricia Arquette), is a medium employed as a consultant for the Phoenix, Arizona district attorney's office. Allison and her husband Joe (Jake Weber) are the parents of three daughters, all of whom inherited Allison's gift. The show was initially based on the experiences of medium Allison DuBois, who claims she has worked with law enforcement agencies across the country in criminal investigations.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Men in Trees</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Men in Trees is an American romantic television dramedy series which premiered on September 12, 2006 on ABC and starred Anne Heche who played relationship coach Marin Frist. The series was set in the fictional town of Elmo, Alaska and concerned Marin Frist's misadventures in relationships. The premise showed at least superficial similarities to the HBO television series Sex and the City (on which series creator Jenny Bicks was a co-executive producer), which also featured a romantically-oriented, female writer. The protagonist's apparent "fish-out-of-water" feeling in a remote, small, Alaskan town can be likened to CBS's Northern Exposure. The protagonists in both series were New Yorkers thrust into small town Alaska societies. Filming for the series was based in Squamish, British Columbia.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Mentalist</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Merlin (2008)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Merlin is a British fantasy-adventure television programme by Julian Jones, Jake Michie, Julian Murphy and Johnny Capps. It began broadcasting on BBC One on 20 September 2008. The show is based on the Arthurian legends of the wizard Merlin and his relationship with Prince Arthur but differs from traditional versions of the legend in many ways. It is produced by independent production company Shine Limited. After a successful first series, U.S. broadcaster NBC began airing the programme on 21 June 2009, but after a decline in viewers, it was moved to the cable network Syfy, where it began broadcasting the second series on 2 April 2010. The second series began airing on 19 September 2009 on BBC One.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Metalocalypse</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 00:15:00(US/Eastern) on Adult Swim</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
        <description>Metalocalypse is an American animated television series, created by Brendon Small and Tommy Blacha, which premiered on August 6, 2006 on Adult Swim. The television program centers around the larger than life death metal band Dethklok and often portrays dark and macabre content, including such subjects as violence, death, and the drawbacks of fame, with extremely hyperbolic black humor and often gets a TV-MA V rating. The show can be seen as both a parody and celebration of heavy metal culture.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Middle</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The Middleman</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Middleman is an American television series. The series, which was developed for television by Javier Grillo-Marxuach for ABC Family, is based on the Viper Comics series, The Middleman, created by Grillo-Marxuach and Les McClaine. The series ran for one season in 2008.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Minute to Win It</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on Game Show Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: On Hiatus</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Minute to Win It is an American prime time game show on NBC hosted by Guy Fieri. Contestants take part in a series of 60-second challenges that use objects that are commonly available around the house.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Miranda</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(Great Britain) on BBC TWO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Miranda is a BBC television series co-written by and starring comedienne Miranda Hart, which first aired on BBC Two on 9 November 2009. The situation comedy also features Sarah Hadland, Tom Ellis, Patricia Hodge, James Holmes and Sally Phillips. The series is based on Hart's semi-autobiographical writing and followed a television pilot and the BBC Radio 2 comedy Miranda Hart's Joke Shop.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Misfits</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(Great Britain) on E4</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Misfits is a British science fiction comedy-drama television series about a group of young offenders forced to work in a community service programme, where they obtain supernatural powers after a strange electrical storm. The first series started broadcasting on 12 November 2009 on E4, and was produced by Clerkenwell Films. The show aired in Australia in 2010 on ABC2. In June 2011, it was made available online in the United States via Hulu,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Modern Family</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Modern Family is an American television comedy created by Christopher Lloyd and Steven Levitan, which debuted on ABC on September 23, 2009. Lloyd and Levitan serve as showrunner and executive producers, under their Levitan-Lloyd Productions label. Depicted in mockumentary style, the fictional characters talk directly into the cameras during many situations that arise throughout the series.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Monk</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on USA</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Monk is an American comedy-drama detective mystery television series created by Andy Breckman and starring Tony Shalhoub as the title character, Adrian Monk. It originally ran from 2002 to 2009 and is primarily a mystery series, although it has dark and comic touches.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Moonlight</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Moonlight is an American paranormal romance television drama created by Ron Koslow and Trevor Munson, who was also executive producer for all episodes with Joel Silver, Gerard Bocaccio, Gabrielle Stanton and Harry Werksman. The series follows private investigator Mick St. John (Alex O'Loughlin), who was turned into a vampire by his bride Coraline (Shannyn Sossamon) on the couple's wedding night fifty-five years earlier. In the present day, he struggles with his attraction to a mortal woman, Beth Turner (Sophia Myles), his friendship with Josef Kostan (Jason Dohring), and his dealings with other vampires in Los Angeles.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>My Boys</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on TBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>My Boys is an American television sitcom that debuted on November 28, 2006, on TBS. The show deals with a female sports columnist in Chicago, Illinois and the men in her life including her brother and her best friend. The show was canceled by TBS on September 14, 2010, making the fourth season finale, broadcast two days prior, the series finale.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>My Family</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>My Family is a British television comedy, created and initially co-written by Fred Barron, which was produced by DLT Entertainment and Rude Boy Productions, and broadcast by BBC One for eleven series between 2000 and 2011, with Christmas specials broadcast from 2002 onwards. My Family was voted 24th in the BBC's "Britain's Best Sitcom" in 2004 and was the most watched sitcom in the United Kingdom in 2008.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>My Name Is Earl</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>My Name Is Earl is an American television comedy series created by Greg Garcia that was originally broadcast on the NBC television network from September 20, 2005 to May 14, 2009 in the United States. It was produced by 20th Century Fox Television and starred Jason Lee as the title character.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>MythBusters</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on Discovery Channel</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>MythBusters is a science entertainment TV program created and produced by Beyond Television Productions for the Discovery Channel. The series is screened by numerous international broadcasters, including Discovery Channel Australia, Discovery Channel Latin America, Discovery Channel Canada, Quest and the Discovery Channel in the UK. The show's hosts, special effects experts Adam Savage and Jamie Hyneman, use elements of the scientific method to test the validity of rumors, myths, movie scenes, adages, Internet videos and news stories.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Naruto (US)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: AJ</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>NCIS</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The New Adventures of Old Christine</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The New Adventures of Old Christine is an American comedy series starring Julia Louis-Dreyfus which ran for five seasons on CBS from March 13, 2006 to May 12, 2010. The show received nine Emmy Award nominations, winning one for Louis-Dreyfus' performance in the first season.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>New Girl</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Nikita</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The Nine Lives of Chloe King</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Nine Lives of Chloe King is an American fantasy drama television series which premiered on ABC Family on June 14, 2011 and ended on August 16, 2011. The series follows Chloe King (Skyler Samuels), a girl who discovers that she is a descendant of an ancient race of Baset offspring called the Mai, as she attempts to learn more about her cat-like powers with her friends and protectors, while also assuming the role of the "Uniter," a warrior that can stop the war between Mai and humans. Chloe is also bestowed with nine lives and must stay alive while dealing with her love life and the mysteries behind her missing father.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Not Going Out</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(Great Britain) on BBC One</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Not Going Out is a British television sitcom that has aired on BBC One since 2006. Starring Lee Mack, Tim Vine, Sally Bretton, Miranda Hart and Katy Wix, it was initially written by Mack, Andrew Collins, Paul Kerensa, Simon Evans and Peter Tilbury, but now features contributions from other writers.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Numb3rs</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Nurse Jackie</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Nurse Jackie is an American series that premiered on June 8, 2009, on Showtime, Movie Central and The Movie Network.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The New Normal</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Once Upon a Time</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Once Upon a Time may refer to:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>One Life to Live</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 14:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>One Life to Live (OLTL) is an American soap opera which debuted on July 15, 1968 and has been broadcast on the ABC television network.One Life to Live was expanded from 30 minutes to 45 minutes on July 26, 1976, and then to a full hour on January 16, 1978.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>One Tree Hill</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>One Tree Hill is an American teen, young adult television drama created by Mark Schwahn, which premiered on September 23, 2003 on The WB Television Network. After its third season, The WB merged with UPN to form The CW Television Network, and, since September 27, 2006, the network has been the official broadcaster for the show in the USA. The show is set in the fictional town of Tree Hill in North Carolina and originally follows the lives of two half-brothers, Lucas Scott (Chad Michael Murray) and Nathan Scott (James Lafferty). Their relationship evolves from heartless enemies to caring brothers, and the basketball drama, as well as the brothers' on-again/off-again romances with female characters, are significant elements within the series.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Outlaw</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Outlaw is an American television series that was aired on the NBC network. The one-hour courtroom drama stars Jimmy Smits as a Supreme Court Justice who resigns from the bench to start his own law firm, as a way to more directly promote the ends of justice. The series premiered on Wednesday, September 15, 2010, and began airing on Fridays beginning September 17. The series finale aired on November 13, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Outsourced</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Outsourced is an American television sitcom set in an Indian workplace. It was based on the John Jeffcoat film of the same name and adapted by Ken Kwapis (In Cahoots Productions) and Universal Media Studios for NBC. The series originally ran from September 23, 2010 to May 12, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Packed To The Rafters</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(Australia/Sydney) on Seven</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: AU</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Pair of Kings</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY XD</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Pair of Kings is an American television sitcom shown on the Disney XD cable channel. It was created by Dan Cross and David Hoge and stars Mitchel Musso and Doc Shaw. The sitcom's target audience are teenagers. The series began production on February 15, 2010</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Pan Am</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Pan Am is a television series centered around the iconic airline Pan American World Airways during the 1960s. The period drama, from writer Jack Orman (ER) and director Thomas Schlamme (The West Wing), will focus on the pilots and flight attendants working for the world-famous airline in 1963.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Parks and Recreation</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Parks and Recreation is an American comedy television series on NBC that focuses on Leslie Knope (Amy Poehler), a mid-level bureuacrat in the parks department of Pawnee, a fictional town in Indiana. Created by Greg Daniels and Michael Schur, the series debuted on April 9, 2009; it has run for three seasons and has currently airing its fourth. Originally conceived as a spin-off to The Office, Daniels and Schur instead created a stand-alone series that shares that show's single-camera, mockumentary filming style.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Party Down</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Starz</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Party Down is an American comedy television series created and primarily written by John Enbom, Rob Thomas, Dan Etheridge, and Paul Rudd that aired on the Starz network in the United States.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Penguins of Madagascar</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 00:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Penguins of Madagascar is an American CGI animated television series airing on Nickelodeon. It stars nine characters from the DreamWorks Animation animated film Madagascar: The penguins Skipper (Tom McGrath), Kowalski (Jeff Bennett), Private (James Patrick Stuart), and Rico (John DiMaggio); the lemurs King Julien (Danny Jacobs), Maurice (Kevin Michael Richardson), and Mort (Andy Richter); and Mason (Conrad Vernon) and Phil the chimpanzees. Characters new to the series include Marlene the otter (Nicole Sullivan) and a zookeeper named Alice (Mary Scheer).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Perfect Couples</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Perfect Couples is an American comedy television series that was originally broadcast by NBC. The half-hour romantic comedy was co-created by Jon Pollack and Scott Silveri and produced by Universal Media Studios. A sneak preview of the series aired on December 20, 2010,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Person of Interest</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>"You are being watched. The government has a secret system: a machine that spies on you every hour of every day. I know, because I built it. I designed the machine to detect acts of terror, but it sees everything. Violent crimes involving ordinary people; people like you. Crimes the government considered 'irrelevant'. They wouldn't act, so I decided I would. But I needed a partner, someone with the skills to intervene. Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret. You'll never find us, but victim or perpetrator, if your number's up... we'll find you".

Season one opening voice-over by Harold Finch</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Persons Unknown</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Persons Unknown may refer to:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Phineas and Ferb</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:15:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
        <description>Phineas and Ferb is an American animated television comedy series. Originally broadcast as a preview on August 17, 2007, on Disney Channel, the series follows Phineas Flynn and his English stepbrother Ferb Fletcher on summer vacation. Every day the boys embark on some grand new project, which annoys their controlling sister, Candace, who tries to bust them. The series follows a standard plot system; running gags occur every episode, and the B-Plot almost always features Perry the Platypus ("Agent P"), acting as a secret agent to fight an evil scientist named Dr. Heinz Doofenshmirtz. The two plots intersect at the end to erase all traces of the boys' project just before Candace can show it to their mother. This usually leaves Candace very frustrated.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Pretty Little Liars</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Primeval</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(Great Britain) on WATCH</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Primeval is a British science fiction television programme produced for ITV by Impossible Pictures. Created by Adrian Hodges and Tim Haines, who previously created the Walking with... documentary series. Primeval follows a team of scientists tasked with investigating the appearance of temporal anomalies across Great Britain through which prehistoric and futuristic creatures enter the present.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Prison Break</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Prison Break is an American television serial drama created by Paul Scheuring, that was broadcast on the Fox Broadcasting Company for four seasons, from 2005 until 2009. The series revolves around two brothers; one has been sentenced to death for a crime he did not commit, and the other devises an elaborate plan to help his brother escape prison. The series was produced by Adelstein-Parouse Productions, in association with Original Television and 20th Century Fox Television. Along with creator Paul Scheuring, the series is executive produced by Matt Olmstead, Kevin Hooks, Marty Adelstein, Dawn Parouse, Neal H. Moritz, and Brett Ratner who directed the pilot episode. The series' theme music, composed by Ramin Djawadi, was nominated for a Primetime Emmy Award in 2006.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Private Practice</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Private Practice is an American medical drama television program which premiered on September 26, 2007 on ABC. A spin-off of Grey's Anatomy, the series chronicles the life of Dr. Addison Montgomery, played by Kate Walsh, as she leaves Seattle Grace Hospital in order to join a private practice in Los Angeles. The series was created by Shonda Rhimes, who also serves as executive producer alongside Betsy Beers, Mark Gordon, Mark Tinker and Jon Cowan &amp; Robert Rovner, who serve as showrunners due to Rhimes's duties on Grey's Anatomy.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Project Runway</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Lifetime</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 90 min</runtime>
        <description>Project Runway is an American reality television series on Lifetime Television, previously on the Bravo network, which focuses on fashion design and is hosted by model Heidi Klum. The contestants compete with each other to create the best clothes and are restricted in time, materials and theme. Their designs are judged, and one or more designers are eliminated each week.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Psych</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on usa network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Pushing Daisies</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Pushing Daisies is an American comedy-drama television series created by Bryan Fuller that aired on ABC from October 3, 2007 to June 13, 2009. The series stars Lee Pace as Ned, a pie-maker with the ability to bring dead things back to life with his touch, an ability that comes with stipulations. The cast also includes Anna Friel, Chi McBride, Kristin Chenoweth, Ellen Greene and Swoosie Kurtz. The series is narrated by Jim Dale.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>QI</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC TWO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>QI (Quite Interesting) is a British comedy panel game television quiz show created and co-produced by John Lloyd, hosted by Stephen Fry, and featuring permanent panellist Alan Davies. Most of the questions are extremely obscure, making it unlikely that the correct answer will be given. To compensate, points are awarded not only for right answers, but also for interesting ones, regardless of whether they are right or even relate to the original question. Conversely, points are deducted from a panellist who gives "answers which are not only wrong, but pathetically obvious", typically answers that are generally believed to be true but in fact are not. Points are also often deducted if an obvious joke answer is given. In addition, bonus points are often awarded or deducted for various challenges or incorrect references to a certain thing or place, varying from show to show.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Raising Hope</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:30:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Raising Hope is a television comedy program first aired on September 21, 2010 on Fox.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Raising the Bar</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on TNT</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Raising the Bar is an American legal drama, which ran on TNT network from September 1, 2008 to December 24, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Real L Word</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The L Word is an American co-production television drama series originally shown on Showtime portraying the lives of a group of lesbian, bisexual, and transgender people and their friends, family and lovers in the trendy Greater Los Angeles, California city of West Hollywood. The show ran from 2004 to 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Real Time With Bill Maher</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Real Time with Bill Maher is a talk show that airs weekly on HBO, hosted by comedian and political satirist Bill Maher. Much like his previous show, Politically Incorrect on ABC (and before that, on Comedy Central), Real Time features a panel of guests that discuss current events in politics and the media. Unlike the previous show, however, guests are usually more well-versed in the subject matter: more experts such as journalists, professors and politicians participate in the panel, and there are fewer actors and celebrities included in it. Additionally, many guests appear via satellite. Also, Politically Incorrect was produced four days a week and was pre-recorded, while Real Time only produces one episode a week which is broadcast live.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Real World</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Real World is a reality television program on MTV originally produced by Mary-Ellis Bunim and Jonathan Murray. First broadcast in 1992, the show is the longest-running program in MTV history,</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Reaper</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on The CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Reaper is an American television series that focuses on Sam Oliver, a "reaper" who works for the Devil by retrieving souls that have escaped from Hell.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Red Dwarf</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC TWO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Regular Show</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Revenge</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Revenge is an American television drama billed as an adaptation of the Alexandre Dumas novel The Count of Monte Cristo</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Riches</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Ridiculousness</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ringer</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on The CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Ringer is a CW television series created by Eric Charmelo and Nicole Snyder, and starring Sarah Michelle Gellar.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ripper Street</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT+0 +DST) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Robot Chicken</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:55:00(US/Eastern) on Adult Swim</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 15 min</runtime>
        <description>Robot Chicken is an American stop motion animated television series created and executive produced by Seth Green and Matthew Senreich along with co-head writers Douglas Goldstein and Tom Root. Green provides many voices for the show. Senreich, Goldstein, and Root were former writers for the popular action figure hobbyist magazine ToyFare.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Royal Pains</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on usa network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Running Wilde</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Running Wild or Runnin' Wild may refer to:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Sadie J</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 17:15:00(Great Britain) on Cbbc</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Samantha Who?</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Samantha Who? is an American television sitcom that originally aired on ABC from October 15, 2007 to July 23, 2009. The series was created by Cecelia Ahern and Don Todd, who also served as producers. Although highly rated during its first season, the sitcom lost momentum and viewers throughout its second season, and ABC canceled the show in May 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Sanctuary (US)</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Sanctuary is a Canadian science fiction-fantasy television series, created by Damian Kindler. The show is an expansion of an eight-webisode series that was released at no cost through the Internet in early 2007. Seeing the success of the web series, Syfy decided to pick up the series for a more traditional television-based 13-episode season.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Saturday Night Live</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 23:30:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 90 min</runtime>
        <description>Saturday Night Live has long mocked the television medium with many fake commercials and parodies of TV shows themselves. Another of the show's frequently used styles of recurring sketches has been the talk show format (eg. "The Brian Fellowes Show", "Barry Gibb Talk Show", etc.). However, anything from cop shows to children's shows has been fair game for the ever-changing cast.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Saving Grace</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on TNT</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Scandal</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Scandal is an upcoming American drama series starring Kerry Washington which will debut on ABC as a mid-season replacement in the 2011/2012 television season.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Scrubs</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Secret Diary of a Call Girl</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on itv2</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Secret Diary of a Call Girl is a British television drama broadcast on ITV2 from 2007-2011 based on the blog and books by the pseudonymous "Belle de Jour," starring Billie Piper as Belle, a high-class London-based call girl. The series was written by Lucy Prebble, who is also known as the author of The Sugar Syndrome and ENRON. The series has been compared to Sex and the City by many critics, mainly due to its humorous approach to sex.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Secret Life of the American Teenager</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Secret Life of the American Teenager (often shortened to Secret Life) is an American teen drama television series created by Brenda Hampton. It first aired on ABC Family on July 1, 2008.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Shake It Up</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Shake It Up is an American television sitcom airing on Disney Channel in the United States. The series premiered on November 7, 2010. Created by Chris Thompson and starring Bella Thorne and Zendaya, the show follows the adventures of Cece Jones (Bella Thorne) and Rocky Blue (Zendaya) as they star as background dancers on a local show, Shake It Up. Although, it is called Shake It Up Chicago on the show, Shake It Up. It also chronicles their misadventures on- and off-set, and their troubles and rising social status at school. Davis Cleveland, Roshon Fegan, Adam Irigoyen, Kenton Duty and Caroline Sunshine also are other main characters in the series. The show's original concept was for Disney to create a female buddy comedy, only with a dance aspect. The dance concept is Disney's third original series, after The Famous Jett Jackson and Sonny with a Chance, to use a show-within-a-show format. The shows theme colors are purple, orange, yellow and pink. The logo also includes neon green and blue.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Shameless</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(Great Britain) on Channel 4</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Shameless is a British drama television series set in Manchester on the fictional Chatsworth council estate. Produced by Company Pictures for Channel 4, the first seven-episode series aired weekly on Tuesday nights at 10pm from 13 January 2004. The comedy drama, centred on British underclass and working class culture, has been accorded critical acclaim by various sections of the British media, including The Sun newspaper and Newsnight Review on BBC Two. The programme was created and partially written by Paul Abbott, who is also the programme's executive producer. The second half of series eight will continue from 30 August 2011 on Channel 4 until October 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Shark</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Shark is an American legal drama created by Ian Biederman that originally aired on CBS from September 21, 2006 to May 20, 2008. The series stars James Woods.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Sherlock</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 90 min</runtime>
        <description>Sherlock is a British television series created by Steven Moffat and Mark Gatiss. It is a contemporary update of Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's Sherlock Holmes detective stories and stars Benedict Cumberbatch as Sherlock Holmes and Martin Freeman as Doctor John Watson. After an unbroadcast pilot was produced in 2009, the first series of three 90-minute episodes was transmitted on BBC One and BBC HD in July and August 2010. A second series of three episodes is due to be broadcast in early 2012.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Shield</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Shield is an American television drama series starring Michael Chiklis which premiered on March 12, 2002 on FX in the United States and concluded on November 25, 2008 after seven seasons. Known for its controversial portrayal of corrupt police officers, it was originally advertised as Rampart in reference to the true life Rampart Division police scandal, which the show's Strike Team was loosely based upon. The first season gained the most Emmy nominations for a basic cable drama. The series was created by Shawn Ryan and The Barn Productions for Fox Television Studios and Sony Pictures Television.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Simpsons</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Simpsons is an American animated sitcom created by Matt Groening for the Fox Broadcasting Company. The series is a satirical parody of a working class American lifestyle epitomized by its family of the same name, which consists of Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie. The show is set in the fictional town of Springfield and parodies American culture, society, television and many aspects of the human condition.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Slide</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(GMT+10 -DST) on FOX8</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: AU</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 42 min</runtime>
        <description>Slide (stylised as SLiDE) is an Australian teen drama series which premiered on the 16 August 2011 on the Fox8 subscription television channel. The series follows the lives and exploits of five teenagers making their way into adulthood in the city of Brisbane, Australia.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Smallville</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Smallville is an American television series developed by writers/producers Alfred Gough and Miles Millar based on the DC Comics character Superman, originally created by Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster. The television series was initially broadcast by The WB Television Network (The WB), premiering on October 16, 2001. After Smallville's fifth season, The WB and UPN merged to form The CW Television Network, which became the broadcaster for the show in the United States. It ended its tenth and final season on May 13, 2011. The series follows the adventures of Clark Kent (Tom Welling), who resides in the fictional town of Smallville, Kansas, during the years before he becomes Superman. The first four seasons focus on Clark and his friends' high school years. After season five, the show ventured into more adult settings, eventually focusing on his career at the Daily Planet, as well as introducing other DC comic book superheroes and villains.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Smash</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Smash is an upcoming American NBC series set to premiere on Monday, February 6, 2012.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>So Random!</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 19:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Sonny with a Chance is an American children's sitcom which aired on Disney Channel, created by Steve Marmel, that follows the experiences of teenager Sonny Munroe, portrayed by Demi Lovato, who becomes the newest accepted cast member of her favorite live comedy show, So Random!.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Sonny With A Chance</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Sonny with a Chance is an American children's sitcom which aired on Disney Channel, created by Steve Marmel, that follows the experiences of teenager Sonny Munroe, portrayed by Demi Lovato, who becomes the newest accepted cast member of her favorite live comedy show, So Random!.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Sons of Anarchy</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on FX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>The Soup</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on E!</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Soup is an E! Entertainment Television weekly series; it is a revamped version of Talk Soup that focuses on recaps of various pop culture and television show moments of the week. The show is hosted by comedian Joel McHale, who provides sarcastic and biting commentary on the various clips.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Southland</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Turner Network Television</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Southland (promotionally styled SouthLAnd) is an American drama</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>South Park</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Comedy Central</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Spooks</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Spooks is a British television drama series produced by the independent production company Kudos for BBC One. The title is a popular colloquialism for spies, as the series follows the work of a group of MI5 officers based at the service's Thames House headquarters, in a highly secure suite of offices known as The Grid. In the United States and France, the show is broadcast under the title MI-5. In Canada, the programme originally aired as MI5 but now airs on BBC Canada as Spooks.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Stargate Atlantis</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Stargate Atlantis (often abbreviated SGA) is a Canadian-American military science fiction television series and part of MGM's Stargate franchise. The show was created by Brad Wright and Robert C. Cooper as a spin-off series of Stargate SG-1, which was created by Wright and Jonathan Glassner and was itself based on the feature film Stargate (1994). The first three seasons of Stargate Atlantis were broadcast by The Sci-Fi Channel and The Movie Network, while the final two seasons aired exclusively on Sci-Fi. The show premiered on July 16, 2004; its final episode aired on January 9, 2009. The series was filmed in and around Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Stargate Universe</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Stargate Universe (often abbreviated as SGU) is a Canadian-American military science fiction television series and part of MGM's Stargate franchise. It follows the adventures of a present-day, multinational exploration team who is traveling on an Ancient spaceship Destiny many billions of light years distant from the Milky Way Galaxy. They evacuated there and are now trying to figure out a way to return to Earth, while simultaneously trying to explore and to survive in their unknown area of the universe. The series, created by Brad Wright and Robert C. Cooper, premiered in the United States on Syfy on October 2, 2009. The series featured an ensemble cast and was primarily filmed in and around Vancouver, BC, Canada. A second season of 20 episodes was announced by Syfy in December 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Storm Chasers</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Discovery Channel</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Storm Chasers is a weekly American documentary reality television series that premiered on October 17, 2007 on the Discovery Channel. Produced by Original Media, the program follows several teams of storm chasers as they attempt to intercept tornadoes in Tornado Alley in the United States. Season 4 commenced on Wednesday, October 13, 2010. Discovery has renewed the series for a fifth season which will premiere on September 25, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Suburgatory</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Suburgatory is an upcoming American television series created and written by Emily Kapnek and co-produced with Michael Fresco for Warner Bros. Television. The series will debut as a Fall 2011 entry on ABC, It is a portmanteau of the words "suburban" and "purgatory".</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Suite Life on Deck</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Suite Life on Deck is an American sitcom that aired on Disney Channel from September 26, 2008 to May 6, 2011. It is a sequel/spin-off of the Disney Channel Original Series The Suite Life of Zack &amp; Cody. The series follows twin brothers Zack and Cody Martin and hotel heiress London Tipton in a new setting, the SS Tipton, where they attend classes at "Seven Seas High" and meet Bailey Pickett while Mr. Moseby manages the ship. The ship travels around the world to nations such as Italy, Greece, India, Sweden and the United Kingdom where the characters experience different cultures, adventures, and situations.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Supernatural</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Swingtown</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Swingtown is an American television series created by Mike Kelley as a summer replacement series for CBS. The show was a period and relationship drama about the impact of sexual and social liberation in 1970s American suburban households, with story arcs involving open marriages and key parties.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Switched at Birth</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on ABC Family</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Switched at Birth is an American television series that premiered on ABC Family on June 6, 2011 at 9:00 ET/PT.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Teen Wolf</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on MTV</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Teen Wolf may refer to:</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Terra Nova</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Terra Nova is an American science fiction drama television series that is scheduled to air on Fox on Monday nights. It is scheduled to begin on September 26, 2011, starting with a two-hour premiere.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Finder</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Finder is an upcoming American procedural drama television series created by Hart Hanson scheduled to premiere midseason on Fox in 2012, airing on Thursdays at 9:00 pm. It is a spin-off of another Fox television series, Bones, with the backdoor pilot episode airing as a part of the sixth season of Bones. The series stars Geoff Stults and Michael Clarke Duncan, with the female lead being recast.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Three Rivers</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Three Rivers is a medical drama, which premiered on CBS on October 4, 2009 and aired Sundays at 9 pm Eastern Time/Pacific Time. The series was set in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania at a fictional hospital specializing in transplants, with Alex O'Loughlin starring as a famous transplant surgeon.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Tittybangbang</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC THREE</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Tittybangbang is a female-led television sketch comedy, performed by Lucy Montgomery and Debbie Chazen, which ran between 2005 and 2007 on BBC Three. The show was largely written by Bob Mortimer and Jill Parker and produced by their company Pett Productions.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Top Chef</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Bravo</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Top Chef is an American reality competition show that airs on the cable television network Bravo, in which chefs compete against each other in culinary challenges. They are judged by a panel of professional chefs and other notables from the food and wine industry with one or more contestants eliminated in each episode. The show is produced by Magical Elves Productions, the same company that created Project Runway.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Torchwood</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC one</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Torchwood is a British science fiction television programme created by Russell T Davies. The series is a spin-off from Davies's 2005 revival of the long-running science fiction programme Doctor Who. The show has shifted its broadcast channel each series to reflect its growing audience, moving from BBC Three to BBC Two to BBC One, and acquiring US financing in its fourth series. In contrast to Doctor Who, whose target audience includes both adults and children, Torchwood is aimed at an older audience.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Touch</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on FOX</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Touch is an upcoming American television series written and created by Tim Kring.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Tower Prep</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Tower Prep is an American-Canadian television series that aired on Cartoon Network. It debuted on October 16, 2010, after the world premiere of Scooby-Doo! Curse of the Lake Monster. The series is created by Paul Dini, a former producer and writer of the DC animated universe. It is Cartoon Network's second one-hour live-action series after Unnatural History.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Trauma</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on NBC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Trauma is a television series which originally ran on NBC from September 28, 2009 to April 28, 2010 and focused on a group of paramedics in San Francisco, California.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Troop</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickToons</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>The Troop is an American-Canadian live-action, single camera comedy-adventure television series about a trio of teenagers who fight and capture monsters and other supernatural phenomena that invade the fictional town of Lakewood. Created and executive produced by Max Burnett, Greg Coolidge and Chris Morgan, the series premiered on Nickelodeon on September 18, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Treme</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>True Blood</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>True Blood is an American television series created and produced by Alan Ball. It is based on The Southern Vampire Mysteries series of novels by Charlaine Harris, detailing the co-existence of vampires and humans in Bon Temps, a fictional, small town in the state of Louisiana. The series centers on Sookie Stackhouse (played by actress Anna Paquin), a telepathic waitress who falls in love with vampire Bill Compton (Stephen Moyer).</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Tudors</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on Showtime</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Tudors is a Canadian produced historical fiction television series filmed in Ireland, created by Michael Hirst and produced for Showtime. The series, named after the Tudor dynasty, is loosely based upon the reign of King Henry VIII of England.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Two and a Half Men</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Two and a Half Men is an American television sitcom which premiered on CBS on September 22, 2003. Starring Charlie Sheen, Jon Cryer, and Angus T. Jones, the show was originally about a hedonistic jingle writer, Charlie Harper; his uptight brother, Alan; and Alan's growing son, Jake. Charlie's free-wheeling life is complicated when his brother gets divorced and moves, along with his son, into Charlie's beach-front Malibu house. The series' premise was revamped in the ninth season, focusing on Alan and Jake moving on with their lives after the death of Charlie with help from their new roommate, Walden Schmidt (Ashton Kutcher), who is also dealing with his own troubles following a bad divorce. The three eventually bond and help each other grow and overcome their losses.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Ugly Betty</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on ABC</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Undercover Boss</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Under the Dome</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>This is a list of media based on work by Stephen King (including the Richard Bachman titles). Note that the sequels are not based on Stephen King's work, except Creepshow 2 and the remakes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Unit</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Unit is an American action-drama television series that focuses on a top-secret military unit modeled after the real-life U.S. Army special operations unit commonly known as Delta Force. The series originally aired on CBS from March 7, 2006, to May 10, 2009.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>United States of Tara</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:30:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>United States of Tara is an American television comedy-drama created by Diablo Cody, which began airing on Showtime in 2009. The series follows the life of Tara (Toni Collette), a suburban housewife and mother coping with dissociative identity disorder.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Unnatural History</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on Cartoon Network</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Unnatural History is a television series produced by Warner Horizon Television for Cartoon Network.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Veep</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(GMT-5 +DST) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Veep is a forthcoming 2012 HBO television comedy series set in the office of a fictional U.S. vice-president. The pilot was written by Armando Iannucci and Simon Blackwell.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Veronica Mars</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on CW</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Veronica Mars is an American television series created by Rob Thomas. The series premiered on September 22, 2004 during television network UPN's final two years, and ended on May 22, 2007, after a season on UPN's successor, The CW Television Network. Veronica Mars was produced by Warner Bros. Television, Silver Pictures Television, Stu Segall Productions, Inc and Rob Thomas Productions.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Victorious</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on nickelodeon</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Victorious (stylized as VICTORiOUS) is an American sitcom created by Dan Schneider for Nickelodeon. The series revolves around aspiring singer Tori Vega, portrayed by Victoria Justice, who attends a performing arts high school called Hollywood Arts, while getting into screwball situations on a daily basis. The series premiered on March 27, 2010.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Walking Dead</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on amc</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
    <show>
        <name>Warehouse 13</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Syfy</airtime>
        <status> Status: Final Season</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Warehouse 13 is an American fantasy television series that premiered on July 7, 2009 on the Syfy network.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Waterloo Road</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(Great Britain) on BBC One</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Waterloo Road is an award-winning British television drama series, first broadcast in the United Kingdom on BBC One on 9 March 2006. Set in a troubled comprehensive school in Rochdale, Greater Manchester, the series focuses on the lives of the schools teacher and students, and confronts social issues, including affairs, abortion, divorce, cancer and suicide.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Weeds</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on SHOWTIME</airtime>
        <status> Status: Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Weeds is an American television comedy created by Jenji Kohan and produced by Tilted Productions in association with Lionsgate Television. The central character is Nancy Botwin (Mary-Louise Parker), a widowed mother of two boys who begins selling marijuana to support her family after her husband dies suddenly of a heart attack. Over the course of the show, she and her family become more entangled in illegal activities.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>White Collar</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on usa network</airtime>
        <status> Status: TBD/On The Bubble</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>White Collar is a USA Network television series created by Jeff Eastin, starring Matt Bomer as con-man Neal Caffrey and Tim DeKay as Special Agent Peter Burke. It premiered on October 23, 2009. In December 2009, White Collar was renewed for a second season that began on July 13, 2010. On September 27, 2010, the USA Network renewed White Collar for a third season with 16 new episodes, which premiered on June 7, 2011.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Wire</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(US/Eastern) on HBO</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Wire is an American television drama series set and produced in and around Baltimore, Maryland. Created and primarily written by author and former police reporter David Simon, the series was broadcast by the premium cable network HBO in the United States. The Wire premiered on June 2, 2002 and ended on March 9, 2008, comprising 60 episodes over five seasons.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Without a Trace</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:00:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>Without a Trace is an American television drama which originally ran on CBS from September 26, 2002 to May 19, 2009. The series was set in New York City and concerned a fictitious FBI Missing Persons Unit.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Wizards of Waverly Place</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:00:00(US/Eastern) on DiSNEY CHANNEL</airtime>
        <status> Status: Canceled/Ended</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Wizards of Waverly Place is a Disney Channel Original television series that premiered on October 12, 2007. It won "Outstanding Children's Program" at the 61st Primetime Emmy Awards in 2009. A film adaptation of the series, Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie, premiered as a Disney Channel Original Movie on August 28, 2009; In 2010, the film adaptation won "Outstanding Children's Program" at the 62nd Primetime Emmy Awards.It will also pass 100 episodes.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Workaholics</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 22:00:00(US/Eastern) on Comedy Central</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Trust Me is an American drama series that began airing on TNT on January 26, 2009 at 10 p.m Eastern/ 9 P.M Central. In Canada, Trust Me can be seen on Super Channel.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Wrong Mans</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 21:00:00(GMT+0 +DST) on BBC TWO</airtime>
        <status> Status: New Series</status>
        <country> Country: UK</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description></description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>The Young and the Restless</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 12:30:00(US/Eastern) on CBS</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 60 min</runtime>
        <description>The Young and the Restless is an American television soap opera created by William J. Bell and Lee Phillip Bell for CBS. The show is set in a fictional Wisconsin town called Genoa City, which is unlike and unrelated to the real life village of the same name, Genoa City, Wisconsin.</description>
    </show>
    <show>
        <name>Zeke and Luther</name>
        <airtime>Airtime: 20:30:00(US/Eastern) on Disney XD</airtime>
        <status> Status: Returning Series</status>
        <country> Country: US</country>
        <runtime> Runtime: 30 min</runtime>
        <description>Zeke and Luther is an American Disney XD sitcom about two best friends setting their sights on becoming the world's greatest skateboarders. The show stars Hutch Dano, Adam Hicks, Daniel Curtis Lee and Ryan Newman (season 1-2).</description>
    </show>
</shows>
